gofish.com 2008-06-22

# Privacy Policy at GoFish Corporation

At GoFish, we recognize the importance of privacy and we are committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users and fostering consumer confidence in the Internet and Internet advertising. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit [www.gofishcorp.com,](http://www.gofishcorp.com/) how we may use that information, when information may be disclosed to anyone, and the choices you have regarding whether and how we gather and use information related to you.  
 **  
COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

Personally identifiable information is information that can personally identify you, such as your name, your e-mail address and your postal address. Information that may be personal in nature, but cannot identify who you are, is not personally identifiable information. For example, your IP address and the type of Web browser you use is personal information, but it is not personally identifiable information because it cannot be used to identify you. 

We do not collect personally identifiable information on this site, except in response to direct inquiries. For example, if you solicit information from GoFish via the website, you may be asked to complete forms which require you to provide personally identifiable information. If so, the personally identifiable information collected is used for the purpose for which it is requested. Contact information for potential clients or persons seeking business information is collected in order to contact those persons to provide information about our services. This information may be stored on our servers in the United States. Such information is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business, but can be amended or deleted upon request. To update your information, please contact your account manager or sales representative.

In addition, if you send us an email in response to a job inquiry, publisher or advertiser inquiry, GoFish will use your email address to deliver the information requested or to respond to those inquiries. This contact information may be stored on our servers in the United States. Such information is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business. To update your information, please contact your account manager or communicate with us at the email address you initially contacted.

If you do not want your personally identifiable information collected online, please do not send us emails or complete forms on our site.  
 **  
COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

The GoFish corporate website uses cookies. A “cookie” is a small text file that contains a string of alphanumeric characters. There are two types of cookies that may be used at the GoFish corporate website: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the “Cookies” folder on your computer and remains in this “Cookies” folder after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer’s memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut off your computer. The GoFish corporate website may also use Web beacons (also called “clear GIFs” or “pixel tags”) in conjunction with cookies. Web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a Web page.

If you have arrived at this website by clicking on a banner ad for one of our products or services, a session cookie may be used. This cookie will contain an identification number for the ad that you clicked on, or will contain an identification number for the site that you were visiting when you clicked on the banner ad. This session cookie helps GoFish’s marketing department determine which of our ads attract the most visitors. If, after you arrive at our site, you choose to request further information from us about our products and services, the personal information that you provide in that request will be linked to the information in the session cookie. This also helps GoFish’s marketing department measure the effectiveness of our advertising. This “linking” will not be used to target future advertisements to you or to send you emails about future goods and services. You will receive emails about our products only if you tell us on the product request page that you want us to send them to you. Because this is a session cookie, it will disappear once you have closed your browser. If you return to our site via another one of our ads, you will appear as a new visitor unless and until you provide further personal information.

The GoFish corporate website may use persistent cookies, Web beacons and information collected in our log files (such as Internet Protocol Address, referring URLs, etc.) about your activity at this site to better understand how the website is used, resolve technical problems, and enhance your experience at this site. Information from website analysis cookies or about website usage is not combined with information from any other GoFish cookie.  

In addition, GoFish may serve ads on this and other websites using our own ad-serving technology. In doing so, one of our ad servers will place or read a unique ad-serving cookie on your computer and will use non-personal information about your browser and your activity at this site to serve ads on this and other sites. The ad-serving cookie is a persistent cookie. If you do not want to receive cookies, you may disable cookies on your browser.

 **INFORMATION SHARING OR DISCLOSURE**

In the event that we contract with a third party to provide some part of the information or service on our website, GoFish may provide your information to such third party, or such third party may collect information from you on our behalf. By written agreement, these third parties are required to implement similar security measures and to process your information only as authorized by GoFish to fulfill the service(s) that they have been contracted to provide. Other than these entities, who act on our behalf, information you provide at this site will not be transferred to unrelated third parties, unless we have your permission to do so. However, please note that information provided to this site may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders.

 **SPECIAL NOTE REGARDING THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT**

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) applies to the online collection of personal information from children under 13. It specifies what a website operator must include in a privacy policy, parent or guardian consent requirements, and what responsibilities a website operator has to protect children's privacy and safety online including restrictions on the marketing to those under 13. At GoFish, we take compliance with COPPA very seriously. In addition to the COPPA information and links you will find on [this website](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy/), GoFish screens all of our publisher sites for COPPA compliance and we educate them as to what is necessary to comply.

 **CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

GoFish has implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect both personal and non-personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure or alteration. Our employees are made aware of and are accountable for compliance with these procedures.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Please note this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page. If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time at [privacymatters@gofish.com.](mailto:privacymatters@gofish.com)

 **CHANGES IN CORPORATE STRUCTURE**

If all or part of the company is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, the information that you have provided at this site may be transferred as part of that transaction. However, GoFish will take reasonable steps to assure that such information is used in a manner consistent with the GoFish privacy policy under which it was collected.

 **OTHER GOFISH WEBSITES**

GoFish also owns and operates the www.gofish.com website. This privacy policy does not cover information collected at that website. Please see the privacy policy at [www.gofish.com](http://www.gofish.com/) to learn how information is collected and used by that website.

 **LINKED WEBSITES**

The Website may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by GoFish. These third party websites are typically subject to their own privacy policies, terms of use, and rules, independent of those of Gofish. These third party websites are not necessarily sanctioned, controlled or monitored by Gofish and GoFish has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party website. GoFish encourages you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of the other websites that you visit before responding to any offer.  
 **  
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacymatters@gofish](mailto:privacymatters@gofish.com).com or write us at:

GoFish Corporation  
706 Mission St., 10th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94103

OTHER REQUESTS  
You may request removal of your personally identifiable information at any time by sending an email to [privacymatters@gofish.com](mailto:privacymatters@gofish.com).  Any consumer who prefers not to provide this information online can send regular mail to the following address: 

GoFish Corporation  
706 Mission St., 10th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94103
